JONATHAN GRBAC

iontygrbac1@gmail.com

iontygrbac1@gm

0430934506

Preston, VIC 3072

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated student completing Bachelor of Software Engineering degree. Experienced in Agile and Scrum environments. Supports project coordination, design and programming needs. Fluent in languages listed in Skills. School projects included building apps, optimizing programs and validating code.

SKILLS

General Skills

- 2013-2018: 5 years of Hospitality experience
- 2018-2019: 1 year of Warehouse experience
- 2019-2022 3 years of Customer Service experience

Programming Skills

- Java, SpringBoot
- C++, C, C#
- Python
- Javascript, React
- Elixir, Phoenix
- UI/UX Tools (Figma etc)
- Proficient with Unix/Linux
- Familiar with TCP/IP and general network programming
- Proficiency with SQL, NoSQL

EDUCATION

RMIT University

Bachelor of Science: Software Engineering *Graduation expected in 10/2024*

St Ignatius College:

High School - Graduated 2016

WORK HISTORY

Tapt - Software Engineering (Work Experience) *Cremorne*, VIC • 08/2023 - Present

- Addressed multiple tickets for bug fixes and hot patches.
- Generated comprehensive documentation for clients.
- Created and delivered intellectual property documentation
- Collaborated with colleagues in stand-up meetings to enhance teamwork.

YourGrocer - Packer/Customer Service

Preston, VIC • 06/2018 - 12/2022

- Delivered exceptional customer service to every customer by leveraging extensive knowledge of products and services and creating welcoming, positive experiences.
- Collaborated with staff members to enhance customer service experience and exceed team goals through effective client satisfaction rates.

Napona, Restaurant - Dishwashing/Kitchenhand

Ocean Grove, VIC • 01/2013 - 01/2018

- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Carried out day-to-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- Demonstrated respect, friendliness, and willingness to help wherever needed.
- Maintained customer satisfaction by clarifying questions about orders and specialty items.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- 2009: Elected School Leader
- 2010: Class Captain
- 2010: 3 Mosaic Awards (Saint Ignatius Awards)
- 2014: Travelled to Indonesia a part of a LOTE Excursion
- 2016: Completion of VCE with a 40+ in Mathematics Methods
- 2021: Achieved HD's in 4/6 subjects undertook in first year of University

REFERENCES

Tracey (Customer Service Manager at YourGrocer) - 0408575857 Will Swinton (Former Employer at Napona) - 52562276